Hey guys, let's welcome to another video, let me show you how to extract information from
the dump the else as file, so here I have a calling machine, so the dump file will be
sitting under here, we perform the dumb point of various videos, so you can use one of
a tool called pipecats, pipecats, okay, so the option is on LSA, it's an LSA local system authority
secrets and you need to do the mini dump as a function and you have to give the file of
else as, okay, so the dump file, okay, so once you execute this command, so it will be the
pipecats will be extracting all the secret that will be sitting under the else as, okay,
okay, so the else as has the username and password of NTL and password of the user, let
me try to crack, we're using the crack station, okay, the password of ABCD123 and
now, so here you can see a DPP keys of the users and you can see the log un-section, log
un-section from a, okay, I was unable to copy the exact NTLM hash there, let me use
the stack station, yeah, the password was in the pass, the exact my password will be a pass,
so I share we have many, many, many credentials that has been listed, so let me explain
what is a DPP key in a upcoming videos, okay, so it will be very useful for the DPP data
protection API key, we'll see that in the next video, okay, cool, this is the command,
the pipecats, LSA, local system authority and mini-dump, so you have to give the else
as dump file here, so my file, probably my file ID, it will be another term directly, this
is my file, else as advanced, which we have dumped using various credential dumping technique,
right, okay, I hope you have a clear understanding about the technique, we'll hop off here
and we'll connect you in the next video guys. Thank you, bye bye.